







PERSONNEL DETAILS

Date of Birth 16 Sep 1993
Nationality India
Marital Status Single
Passport No N4974767

LANGUAGES

- ENGLISH
- HINDI
- MALAYALAM
- TAMIL

HOBBIES

- READING
- PLAYING VIOLIN
- CRICKET

VISHAK GANESH

Personal Relationship Manager

PROFILE DESCRIPTION

B.B.A holder with 2 years of experience in Financial service company and also I am a Diploma in Mechanical Engineering holder with a total 3 years of experience as Assistant engineer in FMCG and Steel industries across India. Holds certifications which includes IOSH (MS), Mechanical Cad, QA/QC and Oil & gas technology.

Able to work in any kind of condition. Excellent communication and presentation skills for management and field personnel. Dedicated to maintain safety on each job site.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hachcap Innovation Private limited (Kerala) Personal Relationship 15/05/2018 to till Present Manager Financial Consultant (Loans and Insurance), Investments (Mutual funds, Stock and securities), Tax Auditing and Accounting

Axtel Industries Limited (Gujarat, India)

Assistant Engineer

29/06/2016 to 14/04/2018

Clients includes- Mondelez, Sweets of Oman, Puratos, Jubilant. Handling in Equipment Projects and Involved in installation & commissioning activities for Spices, Flour and Chocolate manufacturer.

Southern Industrial Piping Company (INDIA)

Pipeline Engineer

02/07/2015 to 15/05/2016 Clients- JSW steel plant

Kingston Oilfield Services (INDIA)

Roustabout

10/01/2015 to 25/6/2015

Client - ESSAR Oils (CBM project)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA)

March 2018

Annamalai University, Anna Nagar, Chennai

Diploma in Mechanical Engineering With 91%

March 2014

Udaya Institute of Technology, DOTE University.

12th (Higher Secondary) with 64%

April 2011

from Govt model BHSS Thycadu.

10th (SSLC) with 80%

March 2008

from MMRHSS, Neermenkara, State Board

SKILLS

- Vision, Strategy and Execution
- Leader ship
- Hazard identification and risk Assessment
- Knowledge of good safety practices
- Developing emergency procedures
- Process Approcah
- Team player
- Time Management skills and Ability to prioritize works

CERTIFICATIONS/LISCENCE

IOSH (Managing safety

May 2018

Certificate no: 503284.

Diploma In Industrial Safety

May 2014

from Global institute of technology, Nagercoil, Tamil Nadu.

DIPLOMA IN OIL AND GAS TECHNOLOGY

December 2014

Techshore Inspection service, Ernakulam, Kerala.

QA/QC (Level II)

Techshore Inspection service, Ernakulam, Kerala.

October 2014

September 2014

Piping and Pipeline Engineering

Techshore Inspection service, Ernakulam, Kerala.

TRAININGS

- Attended a divisional level preliminary training in "Fire Fighting and Rescue Operations" conducted by Government of TamilNadu, Fire and Rescue Service Department.
- > One month of practical training at production as well as at oil field drilling site in Darcy Reservoir Consultancy Services from 14th December 2014.

IT SKILLS

- **Diploma in Mechanical Cadd** (mechanical Auto cadd & creo) Educadd Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala. Jan 2014.
- MS Office (MS Word, MS Excel, Power point)
- Familiar in using IMMS (Inventory management software), Windchill (Drawing Library).
- Tally ERP 9 Accounting software.
- Familiar in using outlook express & browsing the internet.

I hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: India Yours Faithfully
Date: 25/02/2019 Vishak Ganesh